안돼요, 레이첼, 미안해요
No, Rachel, I'm sorry.
지난번 인터뷰 후에
부통령님 일정이 엄청 바빠졌어요
But the VP's schedule
has skyrocketed
since the interview.
그러고 보니 미안해 할 필요가 없군요
Actually, I'm not sorry.
왜 미안하다고 했는지 모르겠네요
I'm not sure why
I just said that.
친구들, 할 얘기가 있어
Boy, I'll tell you something.
지난번 TV 인터뷰는 정말 큰 도박 이였지만,
제대로 성공했지.
That TV interview was a big
gamble, but it really paid off.
- 이거 보세요
- 먼데?
- Look at this.
- What is it?
당신을 “헛소리 하지마 부통령” 이라고 부르네요
They're calling you
the "no-BS VP."
제대로 알고있네
Damn right they are.
내 말은, 전부 거짓말 이였지만,
I mean, I lied and everything,
- 적어도, 진실해 보였잖아
- 우후
- but it sounded true, at least.
- Uh-huh.
분위기 좋네요.
Mood is good.
6년만 더 오늘 같으면 좋겠네요
Just need six more
years like today
그러면, 사람들은 당신을 대통령으로 뽑을꺼에요
and they will vote us POTUS.
부통령님, 내일 기억하시죠
Hey, ma'am, remember tomorrow
건강 달리기에 참가 하실 건데
you've got that
Get Moving Fun Run.
준비하셔야 되지 않을까요?
You probably should prepare,
don't you think?
- 10km
- 맞아요
- It's a 10K.
- Yeah.
- 그 정도 거리는 갑옷 입고도 달릴 수 있어.
- 알았어요
- I can run that thing in a suit of armor.
- Okay.
부통령님, 저는 후원자 식사모임에
가면 안될 꺼 같아요.
Ma'am, I shouldn't go with
you to this donors' brunch.
혹시 모를 의심을 받을 수 있거든요
We don't want to set off
any alarm bells.
맞아요, 그래서 저도 안가는 게 좋겠네요
Oh, yeah. You know what?
Me neither.
좋아, 나 혼자 백만장자들 엉덩이에 키스하러 갈게
Okay, I'll go kiss some hateful
billionaire ass on my own.
발딱 서게 만들어 주지
Give them all donor boners.
- 모두가 당신을 원하고 있어요.
- 그래
- Everyone wants a piece of you, ma'am.
- Yeah.
저를 통해서
Via me.
지금 당장 벤과 얘기할 게 있어
I need to go talk
to Ben right now.
- 갑시다!
- 가자고
- Andale!
- Let's go.
아직까지 대통령은 아무 말도 하지 않고 있습니다.
We haven't heard anything
from the president so far.
우리는 국무부 고위층으로 있는
We've got rumors
of a whistleblower
내부고발자의 소문을 들었습니다.
high up
in the State Department.
머 하는 거야?
What?
What are you doing?
- 사람들이 보면 안돼.
- 알았어요
- I don't want people to see that.
- Okay.
벤의 사무실 밖에 약 자판기를 설치해야 되
They should put those
in a dispenser
- 맞아요
- outside Ben's office, right?
- Yeah.
소환에 대비해서 백악관은
White House
staff are lawyering up
법률 대응팀을 준비하고 있습니다.
in case of subpoenas...
벤
Ben.
- 벤?
- 여당 내 잠재적 대권 도전자에
- Ben?
- We've got the president's own party
관한 소문을 들었습니다.
talking of
a potential challenger...
대통령은 왜 바로 사과하지 않는 거지?
Hey, why doesn't POTUS
just make an apology?
내 말은, 나는 사과했고 한 주 동안
자살한 듯이 지냈잖아.
I mean, I did and I was only,
like, suicidal for a week.
- 안 그래?
- 왜냐하면 그는 엉망이거든, 알았어?
- Huh?
- Because he's a mess, all right?
박쥐로 가득한 동굴 속에 있는 기분일 꺼야
He's got a cave
full of bats in his skull.
나는 스파이 논란의 한가운데 있었다고
I took the heat for the spy.
-그 일에 관해 어떤 신용도 얻지 못한 거야?
-그래
- Don't I get any credit for that at all?
- Yeah.
이제 사법위원회가
무차별적으로 우리를 소환하려고 해
So now we've got the House
Judiciary Committee
subpoenaing us senseless.
And on top of that,
we got a rumor going around
가장 흥미로운 것은 정당 내에
대권 도전자가 있다는 소문이야.
that says that there's
a challenger inside the party.
- 머야? 누구?
- 나도 몰라
- What? Who?
- I don't know.
카다피의 아들 중 한 명 일거야.
걔네들이 투표는 더 잘 하니까
One of Gaddafi's sons.
They're polling better.
그러니, 너에겐 정말 고마운데
So thank you very much
for your help,
혼자서 먼저 행동하는 거 좀 제발 그만둬 줄래?
but would you quit being
so goddamned proactive?
앙코르로 멀 또 할 건데?
What are you going
to do for an encore?
개막식 투구 세례머니를 망쳐버릴 거야?
Blow the opening day pitch
out of your ass?
그거 괜찮네
Ah, that's lovely.
다음 2년도 이런 식으로 흘러가는 거야?
Is this what this is going to
be like for the next two years?
맞아
Oh, my, yes.
우리는 심각한 상황에 처해 있다고
We are at DEFCON fuck.
부통령님 기부자들 명단을 외어 볼까요?
Hey, ma'am, I got
flash cards on the donors.
싫어
다 알고 있어
No, thanks.
I got it.
피터 스피닥
곁에 총을 두고 자고
Peter Spiddock
sleeps with his gun,
산드라 오닐
Fracking 을 끔직히 싫어하지
Sandra O'Neill
fricking hates fracking,
시드니 퍼셀
그와 얘기하는 건
Sidney Purcell...
talking to him,
죽은 쥐들로 가득 찬
하수구 관에 끼여있는 거 같아
it's like being stuck in a sewer
pipe filled with dead rats.
그는 태워 없앨 만큼 돈이 많아요
He's got money to burn.
당신에게 기부하는 게 그렇다는 건 아니고요
Not that donating to your
campaign is burning money.
오늘 모임이 어떤 건지 잘 알아
I know what this is all about.
오늘날의 정치적인 유희 같은 거야
This is a political
prick tease today.
네, 그리고 지금 막 시작하려는 중이죠
Yeah, and we're about
to meet a bunch of pricks.
맞아
Yeah.
Challenger schmallenger.
오늘 모임이 잘 끝나면,
I mean, if this
brunch goes well,
선거 자금문제는
my campaign launchpad
is going to be made
완전히 해결 될거야
of solid fucking gold.
그러면 6년 후,
미스 대통령이 나오는 거지.
And then in six years,
it's gonna be Ms. President.
예아!
Yeah!
더 큰 가방이 필요할 꺼 에요!
We're gonna need a bigger bag!
백악관에 여성들을!
Ovaries in the Oval Office!
서부의 자궁!
The West Womb!
뭐?
What?
- 뭐?
- 그거 있잖아요, 자궁
- What?
- You know, like a womb.
애기가 나오는...
Like a woman has a womb
that the baby comes...
오, 애처롭네요
‘폴리티코’지가 발표했는데
Oh, pathetic. "Politico" is announcing
that Danny Chung
대니 청이 방금 ‘내가 귀 기울이는 것’
이란 음악 목록을 Spotify.com 에 올렸대요
has just uploaded his "What I'm
Listening To" playlist on Spotify.
흠, 우리도 해야 돼
Hmm. We need
to do a playlist.
-글쎄요, 우리는 할 필요가...
-아냐 반드시 해야 되
- - No, we don't.
Oh, we absolutely do.
- 댄 에게 연락해
- 아뇨, 제가 할 수 있어요
- Get Dan.
- No, I can help with the songs.
제 조카가 케이티 페리를 좋아해요.
You know, my niece
loves Katy Perry.
방금 말했지, 댄 에게 연락해
Just like I said, get Dan.
- 여기 오는군
- DJ 댄
- There he is.
- DJ Dan.
- 음악들 고마웠네
- 별 말씀을요
- Thanks for the playlist.
- Oh, my pleasure.
장년층과 젊은 청어들 모두에게
잘 통하는 거 같아요
Seems like it's playing
pretty well, too,
with the oldies
and the Young Chungers.
젊은 청어.
The Young Chungers.
- 그게 표어로 생각 한 건가?
- 맘에 드세요?
- It's like you think in hashtags.
- Oh, you like that?
좋아요, 그럼 이건 어때요?
All right, maybe we can call
65세 이상은
그래니청
the over 65ers
the Granny Chungs.
아님, 더 생각해 보죠
Something.
No, I'll keep working on that one.
오, 제길
Oh, shit.
받아 봐.
그녀를 행복하게 해줘.
You need to take that.
Keep her happy.
힘든 요구네요.
Tall order.
돈 냄새가 나지?
You smell that?
Money.
헤이 댄?
Hey, Dan?
-부통령님
-대니 청의 음악리스트에 대해 들은 거 있어?
- Ma'am.
- Have you heard anything about
this Danny Chung playlist?
사실은, 방금 알았네요
I just caught that, actually.
거기도, 스마트한 멤버가 있나 보네요
Some smart stuff on there, too.
젊은이들에겐 나스의 노래를
Nas for the young folks,
은퇴자들에겐 딘 마틴의 노래를
some Dean Martin
for the retirees.
대니 청의 엉덩이 로봇이 한 것처럼
He just got one of his
butt droids to do it,
네가 같은 걸 해줬음 좋겠어, 알았지?
which is why I want you
to do it for me, okay?
명령대로 하죠
Your mix is my command.
수 제발, 좀 도와줘, 네가 잘 하는 거잖아.
Come on, Sue, help me out with this, okay?
You're good at this stuff.
너는 젊고, 유행에도 민감하잖아.
You're young, you're
hip, you're hop.
지미 클리프는 어때?
"The Harder They Come"?
What about Jimmy Cliff?
안돼
No.
보세요, 그게 누군지도 모른다고요,
그러니, 안돼요.
Look, I have no idea
who that is, so, no.
엘비스 코스텔로
"Peace, Love and Understanding"?
Elvis Costello, "Peace,
Love and Understanding"?
- 머?
- 안돼요,안돼요, 그리고 안돼요
- What?
- No, no, and no.
전부 네 아이팟에서 구한 거야?
Are you getting these
all from your iPod?
- 아뇨 웹에 있는 거에요
- 아
- No. I think it's in a cloud.
- Oh.
있잖아, 네가 생각하기에는
You know, do you think
that Danny Chung's
대니 청이 2년 내에 움직이기 시작할까?
the one who's getting ready
to bust a move in two years?
글쎄요, 대권 경쟁이 시작되면,
Well, the way POTUS is going,
빠르던 느리던 아마도 전쟁에 띄어들 거에요.
he'll probably stumble
into a war sooner or later.
그리곤, 사망하게 되겠죠.
Chung will reenlist and
hopefully get himself killed.
내가 왜 대니청과 같은 존경을 받지 못하는지
알 수가 없어, 넌 알아?
I don't understand why I don't get the
same respect as he does, you know?
- 이런!
- “존경” 이거 어때?
- Shit!
- Oh, what about that? "Respect."
- 수?
- 아레사 프랭클린 노래 알아?
- Sue?
- You know, the Aretha Franklin song?
- 예.
- 예,예,예
- Yes.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 그거 정말 좋은데요
- 헤이, 마이크.
- That would be great.
- Hey, Mike. Mike.
- 오!
- 맙소사
- Ooh!
- Oh, my God.
공작부인이 쓰러졌다. 공작부인이 쓰러졌다
비상, 비상
Duchess is down. Duchess is down.
Yellow, yellow.
-반복한다, 공작부인이 쓰러졌다, 릭 움직여
가,가,가,가!
- - I repeat, Duchess is down. Go, Rick.
Go, go, go, go!
맙소사, 얼굴 좀 보세요!
Oh, God, your face!
- 의사가 필요하다
- 안 좋은가?
- We're gonna need a medic.
- Is it bad?
- 아뇨
- 네!
- No.
- Yes!
괜찮아요, 부통령님
괜찮아요
You're fine, ma'am.
You're fine.
부통령님, 거기 가만히 계세요
Madam Vice President, if you'd
just stand still, please.
- 진정해 마틴. 테러도 아니잖아.
- 난 괜찮아
- Calm down, Martin. It's not a terrorist.
- I'm fine.
통로를 막아, 제군들.
모두 괜찮아.
Just lock up the hallway, guys.
It's all fine.
- 통로 봉쇄, 통로 봉쇄
- 부통령님
- Lock it up. Lock it up.
- Ma'am.
- 왜?
- 이렇게 할거에요
- Yes?
- Here's what you do.
- 알았어
- 움직이지 마시고
- Okay.
- Don't move.
옷을 자를 거에요
We're gonna have to cut
your clothes off you.
- 뭐?
- 그 전에 제가 지나 갈게요
- Huh?
- I walked through a glass door before.
- 이렇게 할거에요, 아셨죠?
- 제정신이야?
- This is what you do, okay?
- You're kidding.
아뇨, 전 괜찮아요. 술 취했거든요
No, I was fine
because I was drunk.
- 괜찮을 거에요
- 오
- You're gonna be okay.
- Oh.
- 제길, 후원자 모임
- 지금 바로 가서 전해
- Shit, the donors.
- Just go tell them
몇 분 후에 갈 거라고
I'm gonna be
a couple minutes late.
- 가서 전해, 알았지?
- 알았어요
- Go tell them that, okay?
- Okay, okay.
- 마이크, 머 하는 거야!
- 죄송해요
- All right. What are you... no! Mike!
- Sorry, sorry, sorry.
- 오, 제길!
- 맙소사!
- Oh, shit!
- Oh, my God!
-죄송해요
-하지마...
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Don't... don't...
- 딴 길로 가, 마이크
- 네
- go another way, Mike.
- Okay. Okay.
부통령님 다쳤어요?
Ma'am, ma'am, are you hurting?
아프세요?
Are you in pain?
음, 모르겠어
Uh, I don't know.
거울 있어?
Do you have a mirror?
- 아뇨.
- 아니, 가지고 있잖아
- No.
- Yes, you do.
저한테 통증을 줄여주는 약초가 있는데 드실래요?
I've got some St. John's Wort
for pain relief if you want it.
약 먹기 싫어
I don't want
to take medication.
약초에요
자연에서 온 거죠
It's herbal.
It's from the earth.
6개만 드시면, 몸에 나쁘지 않을 거에요
You can take six,
it won't affect you.
보세요.
Look at that.
아우!
Ah! Ow!
안녕하세요
Hiya. Uh, hey.
음, 부통령님께서 사과하시길,
Uh, the vice president
apologizes,
좀 늦어 지신답니다.
but she's slightly delayed.
호주 대사랑 전화 통화 중이세요.
She's stuck on a call with
the Australian ambassador.
호주 대사?
The Australian ambassador?
좋은데.
한번도 들어본 적 없는 핑계군.
That's good.
I've never heard that one before.
시드니 퍼셀, 만나서 반갑네요.
Sidney Purcell,
always a pleasure, sir.
아니, 안 반가워
하지만, 노력은 가상하게 봐주지
No, it's not, actually,
but you get marks for trying.
부통령님은 여러분과의 만남을
But the vice president
is in great spirits.
학수고대하고 있습니다.
She's buoyantly waiting
to meet you all
제가 다시 가서 체크 해보고 오죠
and I will go check, see if
I can interrupt that call.
다시 말씀 드리지만, 전화 통화 때문이에요
Like I said, it's a call.
권력은 유연하며 확고해야 합니다
Strength is being
flexible and steadfast.
죽은 떡갈나무가 아닌
살아있는 버드나무 처럼 말이죠
The living willow,
not the dead oak.
이라크에서 저는 존경은
I learned in Iraq
that the road to respect
서로 간에 주고 받는 거 란걸 배웠습니다
between me and my men
ran two ways.
존경 받기 위해선, 존경 해야만 합니다.
In order to get respect,
you have to give respect.
둘러보면,
많은 분들의 얼굴이 보이는데,
When I look out,
I see many faces,
저에겐 하나의 열망을 가진
but I see only one nation
하나의 국가만이 보입니다.
with one aspiration,
그리고 그 열망은 언젠가
모두 함께 꿈을 이루는 것입니다.
and that aspiration is to one
day hope to dream together.
-젊은 여성을 만났는데...
-설마
- I met a young woman...
- No.
세인트 폴의 후아니타란 분이였습니다.
Named Juanita
in St. Paul the other day.
-망할
- - Oh, crap.
And I asked...
그녀가 제게 한말은
You know what she said to me?
오.
Oh.
- 댄
- 이거 난처하네
- Dan.
- This is awkward.
난교 파티에서 네 여동생이랑
눈이 마주친 기분이야
Like catching your
sister's eye at an orgy.
글쎄, 내 동생은 절대로 난교파티에 가지 않아.
Well, my sister
would never be at an orgy.
보수적이거든.
Too uptight.
모든 이들에게 건강 기록지를 들이 밀고
She would want health
records from everyone
- 파티를 망쳐 버리려 할거야
- 좋아.
- and just kill the momentum and...
- Okay.
너한테 실망 했어
I'm disappointed in you.
이건 내가 할 만한 행동이지
This is behavior I would
expect from myself.
근데 너? 아니지
But from you? Uh-uh.
헛소리 집어 치우고.
우리 둘 다 청 때문에 여기 온 거야.
Let's cut the crap.
We're both here for Chung.
그러면 우리 함께 뛰어 들었군.
부치랑 선댄스 처럼
So we both jump together.
You know, Butch and Sundance.
둘 다 죽지 않나?
Don't they both die?
아니, 뛰어 들 땐 아냐.
끝에 가서 죽지
No, not when they jump.
They die at the end.
오
Oh.
안녕, 수
Hey, Sue.
댄, 부통령이 방금 유리문에 부딪혔어
Dan, the vice president just
walked through a glass door.
유리문에 부딪혔다고?
She walked through
a glass door?
무슨 말이야, 암호인가?
What is that, code?
아니, 불행히도, 그게 아니고, 댄
No, unfortunately,
it is not, Dan.
문자 그대로야
It is a literal description
of what just happened.
그리고 물어 봐서 고마운데
그리 많이 다치진 않았대.
And she's not too badly hurt.
Thanks for asking.
유리문에 부딪혔다고?
She walked through
a glass door?
맞아, 부통령은 그녀의 커리어처럼
행동하기로 했나 보군
Yeah, that woman has become a
living metaphor of her own career.
오늘은 쉬셔야 돼요, 아시겠죠?
Just make sure
you rest today, okay?
고아원 아이들이 쓰도록 수선한
오래 되고 낡은 축구공이 된 기분이야
I feel like one of those
old used footballs
that they fixed up for the kids
at an orphanage.
조용히 열어줘서 고맙네.
Good to see you've calmed down.
부통령님, 푹 쉬시고
내일 10km 달리기는 안돼요
Ma'am, plenty of rest
and no 10K run tomorrow.
- 아셨죠?
- 글쎄, 확신 할 수는 없어
- Okay?
- Well, I don't know about that.
- 왔나
- 다녀 왔어요
- Hey.
- Hi.
음, 모두에게 늦어 진다고 얘기 했는데
Uh, we told everyone
you were delayed.
이번 모임은 취소 해야겠어요,아시겠죠?
But we're gonna have
to cancel this thing, okay?
안돼. 마이크,
무슨 얘길 하는 거야?
No. Mike, what are
you talking about?
절대로 취소하면 안돼.
I can't cancel my destiny.
부통령님 차림을 보세요
가운을 걸치고 있잖아요.
Ma'am, look at you.
You're wearing a robe.
지금 꼴로 내려가면
Unless you want to go down
there and sing them a chorus
웃음 거리만 될 거에요
of "Look At Me, I'm Sandra Dee,"
you can't go downstairs.
저는 그만 가볼게요
Okay, I'll go ahead and go.
도와줘서 고마웠어요
Thank you very much
for your help.
- 함구해 주실 거죠?
- 물론이죠.
- Mum's the word?
- Oh, yes.
- 좋아요.
- 머라고 해야 하나?
- Good.
- What would I even say?
그냥 사실대로 말하고
일정을 다시 잡아요
We'll just tell them
what happened and reschedule.
-아우
-맙소사
Oh! Ooh.
- Jesus.
- Oh, God.
취소할게요.
I'm cancelling.
- 부통령님 어디 계시지?
- 나도 몰라
- Okay, where is she?
- I don't know.
그녀의 피랑 개리의 눈물을 따라가면 될 거야
I guess we just follow the trail
of her blood and Gary's tears.
- 오,안녕
- 그녀는 어때요?
- Oh, hey.
- How bad is she?
괜찮아요
피부가 약간 긁힌 거에요
She's fine.
It's just superficial cuts.
진통제나 다른 약을 드렸어요?
Did you give her
any painkillers or...?
약초를 이미 드셔서 안 드렸어요.
I didn't want to do that because
she's already on St. John's Wort.
나도 성당 소녀에게 한번 뺏어 먹은 적이 있지
I think I got that off
a Catholic schoolgirl once.
그럼 다른 거라도 처방 할 수 없나요?
So why can't she take
anything else?
글쎄, 이미 면역억제제, 베타 차단제나
Well, it can react
badly with the body
항우울증약을 드시고 계셔서
if she's already on
immunosuppressants,
부작용을 일으킬 수 있거든요.
beta-blockers,
or antidepressants.
아, 알았어요.
그런데 그녀는 그 중 어떤 것도 하지 않아요
Oh, okay, fine.
She's not on any of those.
저는 이만 가봐야겠네요.
다음에 뵙죠
I've really got to go.
Catch you guys later.
그래요, 고마워요
Yep, thank you.
- 항우울증제를 드셨군.
- 그래
- Well, she is on antidepressants.
- Yep.
숙녀 먼저
After you.
봤지? 참 자연스럽게 지나가잖아.
See? You made that
look so easy.
부통령님,
귀빈실을 구하지 못해서 죄송해요
Hey, I'm sorry this isn't
the presidential suite, ma'am.
괜찮아 개리
Oh, it doesn't matter, Gary.
귀빈실엔 누가 있는데?
Who has the presidential suite?
제가 듣기론 러셀 크로우라고
I heard Russell Crowe.
러셀 크로우 ’글래디에이터’
네
- Russell Crowe, "Gladiator."
- Yeah.
‘곧 돌아 올게’
"I'll be back."
Mmm...
- 이 가운 누가 좋아 하는지 알아?
- 누구요?
- You know who would love this robe?
- Who?
- 벤
- 네,그래요
- Ben.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
벤이 가운을 입고 큰 머그잔을
들고 있는 모습을 상상해봐
Can you imagine him in this
with his big mug?
- 네,네
- 돌아 다니면서?
- Yep, yep.
- Walking around?
그러는 거 좋아하죠
He'd love that.
- 이리 와서 여기 앉아
- 네, 그거 좋겠네요
- Come on, sit here.
- Okay, that's nice.
- 감사합니다.
- Yeah.
- Thank you, ma'am.
너에 대해 잘 모르는 거 같아
I don't really know anything
about you, you know?
신비한 남자지
You're kind of a mystery man.
Ooh.
어디서 자랐어?
Where'd you grow up?
알라바마주, 버밍햄요
Birmingham, Alabama.
설마
You did not.
맞아요
I did too! I did!
- 부모님과 가까웠니?
- 어머니랑은요
- Are you close to your parents?
- Close to my mom.
-아버지는 항상 남자다움을 원했죠, 그래서...
My dad always wanted
a man for a son, so...
- 아 알겠어.
- 세대가 다르니까요
- Oh, yeah.
- But it's a different generation.
세대가 다르지
맞아
It is a different generation.
It's true.
곧 40번째 결혼 기념일이에요
They're about to celebrate
their 40th wedding anniversary.
- 4-0.
- 와!
- Oh!
큰 잔치를 열려고 해요
They're gonna have
a huge blowout.
- 무슨 말이야? 파티?
- 엄청나게 큰 파티죠
- What do you mean? Like a party?
- Massive party.
엄청나게 큰
Massive.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 그건 정말로...
- 내가 가도 될까?
- It's really...
- Can I come?
- 네?
- 내가 가도 되겠냐고
- What?
- Could... Can I come?
정말이에요?
Are you serious?
내가 가는 건 부적절 한가?
Is that completely inappropriate
for me to invite myself?
맙소사, 아니에요
Oh, my God, no.
정말로 좋아요
No. They...
I would love that.
- 그걸 말이라고
- 정말이야?
- Are you kidding?
- Really?
그럼요
Yes.
아버지가 저를 완전히 인정 하실 거에요
That would solve all of my
validation issues with my dad.
부통령님
좀,어떠세요?
Ma'am.
Uh, how are you?
에이미, 이거 좀 봐
Look, Amy, watch this.
얼굴 정말 작게 만들 수 있어
Look how tiny
I can make myself.
봐봐
Watch this.
근데 기부자 모임은 취소된 거죠?
But the donor meeting
has been cancelled, yes?
그거 안 할 거야
I'm not doing that thing.
진지하게,
그 사람들 전부 엿먹으라고 그래
Seriously,
screw all those people.
이란이 워싱턴에 핵이라도 떨구면 좋겠어
God, I hope Iran
drops a nuke on DC.
- 그럼 많은 문제가 한꺼번에 해결될 텐데 말이야
- Ooh.
- Wouldn't that solve a lot of issues?
켄트가 여기 저기 돌아다니는 거만 빼고
Except Kent wouldn't
go anywhere.
그 놈은 그래도 여전히 돌아 다닐걸
He'd still be around.
그 놈은 좀비 바퀴벌레 같아
He's like an undead
cockroach with his...
정말이야
It's true.
얼빠진 얼굴을 하고 있겠지
He's got that blank look.
장담하는데 어디서 나타날지도 모를 거야
I bet he doesn't
even have a come face.
그런 괴물이 상상이 돼?
Can you imagine
fucking that guy?
Whoa.
Amy, you have
such pretty blonde hair.
에이미, 너 정말 이쁜 금발을 가졌네
그렇지 않아?
Doesn't she?
네 정말 이쁘네요
So pretty.
안녕하세요
한번 더 좋은 아침이에요
Hi, everyone.
Good morning again.
안타깝게도, 부통령께서 여전히
Unfortunately, the vice
president is still stuck
호주 대사와 전화통화 중입니다
on a phone call with Australia
그래서 이번 모임을
so she's going to have
to postpone
연기 하려고 합니다.
this morning's meet and
greet breakfast, okay?
정말 죄송합니다
We're very sorry.
마이크 그거 아나?
남반구에서는
Mike, you know,
in the southern hemisphere,
헛소리는 실제로 반대로 흘러가지
the bullshit actually
flows the other way.
알고 있어?
Did you know that?
- 호주 건은 사실이에요
- 그렇겠지
- The Australia thing is real.
- Yeah.
- 도대체 무슨 일이야?
- 알았어요, 들어보세요
- What the fuck?
- Okay, listen to me.
부통령님께 사고가 생겼어요
There's been an incident
with the vice president.
- 비밀로 해주실래요?
- 그래, 먼데?
- Can you keep this under wraps?
- Yeah. What?
유리문을 통과하려다 부딪혔어요
She's walked through
a glass door.
- 유리문에 부딪혔다고?
- 쉬!
- She walked through a glass door?
- Shh!
머야, 유리문을 들이 받았다고?
What, she just stumbled
into a solid piece of glass?
네
Yes.
그거... 놀라운데
That's... that's amazing.
다같이 동시에 웃다니
I guess it's funny
재미있네요
because we've all
done it at one point.
난 아닌데.
I haven't.
나도 누군가를 유리문 뒤에서 민 적이 있지
I pushed someone through
a plate glass door once.
정말로 웃겼어
That was fucking hilarious.
그만 웃어요
Stop laughing.
부통령님은 괜찮으세요?
Is she okay?
네. 살짝 긁혔어요
Mm. Just cuts.
너는 부통령의 연락책이야, 그렇지?
You are liaison
to the VP, right?
그게 너의 존재의 이유고?
That's your "liaison d'?re"?
연락책이 제 운명이죠
I was born to liaise, sir.
그럼 부통령이 빌어먹을 유리문에 부딪혔을 때
Then why can't you tell me
about what the VP was doing
그녀가 왜 거기에 있었는지 얘기 좀 해 보지?
when she walked into
a glass fucking door?
그게, 부통령 사무실 직원들은
저를 졸로 봐요
Okay, well, the VP's office
can be very insubordinate.
그들은 언제나 제 말을 무시한다고요
I mean, they insubord me
all the time.
저를 조나드라고 부른다니까요
You know that
they call me Jonad?
제 말은,그건 대통령을 조나드라고
부르는 거와 같은 거에요
I mean, that is tantamount
to calling the president Jonad.
아니지, 그건 아냐
No, it's not.
대통령은 대통령이고
너는 조나드지
He's the president,
you're Jonad.
그럼 저기 들어가서
수에게서 진실을 알아내와
Now get in there and liaise
the truth out of Sue
안 그럼 너의 묘비에다
or I'll make sure
that name sticks so hard,
조나드라고 새겨주지
it ends up on your gravestone.
알겠습니다.
Yes, sir.
좋은 날이야, 수잔
Hello there, Susan.
내 이름은 수잔이 아니고 수야
조나드
Name's not Susan,
it's Sue... Jonad.
좋아, 내 이름은 조나드가 아니야!
Okay, and my name isn't Jonad!
조나라고.
나에게 무례하게 행동하지 마, 수.
It's Jonah.
Do not disrespect me on this, Sue.
워,워,워
여기 아무도 너에게 무례하지 않아
Whoa, whoa, whoa, no one
here is disrespecting you...
조나드
Jonad.
가서 이름이나 바꿔
Now go earn your name change.
-수
-벤
- Sue.
- Sir.
오늘 아침 부통령이 그 호텔엔 머 하러 갔지?
What was the vice president doing
at that hotel this morning?
미국교사협회(ATA)랑 만나러 갔어요
Meet and greet with the
American Teachers Association.
내가 ATA 에 연락 하면
If I call the ATA,
they would confirm
부통령이 그들과 만난걸
확인해 줄까?
that she was meeting
and greeting them?
음, 확신 할 수가 없네요
Uh, couldn't say.
그녀가 멀 했는지 얘기할 수 없다면
If you can't tell me
what she was doing,
그녀가 멀 하지 않았는지
얘기해주는 건 어때
maybe you can tell me
what she wasn't doing.
부통령님은
The vice president
was not at a brunch
선거 후원자들과 만나지 않았습니다.
with campaign donors.
그러지 않았기를 바라네.
I would hope that she was not.
그렇지 않다면,
Otherwise, I'm not sure
지금 바로 무인기로 폭격하지 말라고
if I wouldn't be
within my rights
명령하지 않을 수 없을 지
확신할 수가 없거든.
not to launch a drone
strike right now.
이중 부정 땜에 헷갈렸는데 말입니다.
I got lost in
the double negative, sir.
뭐라구요?
What?
나 지금 열 받았다고.
I'm fuckin' furious.
조나드!
Jonad!
- 넵.
- 호텔로 꺼져.
- Yes, sir.
- Get over to that hotel.
필요하다면 머리를 잘라서
부통령에게 내밀어
Cut your face off and give it
to the VP if you have to.
그리고 언론에 얘기하게 해
Just get her to talk
to the press.
부통령은 대선 경쟁자가 아니라고
Say she is not the challenger.
실망시키지 않겠습니다.
I won't let you down, sir.
- 헤이
- 네
- Hey.
- Yeah.
그 파티 정말 기대되네
I'm really excited
for that party.
저도요
우리 춤추죠
I am, too.
We'll dance.
함께 춤춰요
We'll get our dance on.
춤춰
Dance on.
왜 그리 긴장하고 있어?
부통령님은 완전히 느긋한데
Why are you guys so tense?
She's completely chilled.
그녀는 완전히 정신이 나갔어
She's out of her fucking mind.
우리 부모님 40번째 결혼 기념일에
오시기로 했는데?
She's coming to my parents'
40th wedding anniversary.
그래, 그러니까, 개리
Yeah, exactly, Gary.
그녀는 완전히 정신이 나갔다니까.
She's out of her fucking mind.
부통령님.
후원자 모임을 취소했는데요,
Hey, ma'am.
I cancelled the donor breakfast,
유리문에 부딪혔다는 걸 밝혀야 했어요
but I did have to come clean about
you walking through the glass door.
잘했어, 멍청아
이제 모두 알게 됐네
Great job, ass hat.
Now everyone's gonna know.
그녀 모습을 보고 나면
Everyone's gonna find out she
walked through a glass door, Dan,
유리문에 부딪혔다는 걸 모를 리가 없잖아.
because she looks like she walked
through a fucking glass door.
맞아, 내 꼴을 보라고
Yeah, check this out.
- 쟤 머가 문제야?
- 저도 몰라요
- What's his problem?
- I don't know.
일루 와봐, 생강빵
Get over here, gingerbread.
니가 그녀에게 준 약초가
You know what? That St.
John's Wort that you gave her
항우울증제랑 부작용을 일으키고 있어
is reacting
to her antidepressants.
무슨 말이야?
What are you talking about?
그건 약초라고
자연에서 온 거지
It's herbal.
It's from the earth.
- 버섯도 그래, 병신아
- 그건 불법 약물이고
- So are mushrooms, dipshit.
- Okay, that's illegal drugs.
- 여기 만져봐
- Feel this. Feel this.
- The guns?
- Jesus.
- Argh argh!
- Okay. Hey!
- I'll hurt ya.
- 때려 주지
- 기분이 좋으신 거 같네요
- 그래
- Wow, you're in a good mood.
- I am.
- 요즘 어때?
- 그냥 그래요.
- How are you doing?
- So-so, you know?
좋진 않지만, 노력하고 있죠
Not great, but trying
to keep things on an even keel.
네 보트는 어때?
Hey, what about
that boat of yours?
아직 못 팔고 있어요
I can't sell it.
Nobody wants to buy her.
얼마나 받으려고 한다고?
How much do you want for her?
정직하게, 반값에 팔려고 하고 있죠
Honestly, I would take half just
to get rid of the damn thing.
내가 정가에 사줄게
I'll give you all of it.
- 제 보트를 사시겠다고요?
- 그래
- You really want to buy my boat?
- Yeah.
악수해야지, 마이크
Shake on it, Magic Mikey.
-제 보트를 사신다고요?
- 맞아
- You're gonna buy my boat?
- I am.
- 축하 드려요!
- 너도 축하해
- Congratulations!
- Congratulations to you.
보트가 생기셨네요
You just got a boat.
-그리고 표도 생겼지
마이크!
- - And I just got a vote.
Mike!
마이크, 여기 좀 와봐
간다고, 가
Mike, you're needed in here.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
밖에 방송국 차량이 왔어, 마이크
There's fucking press vans
outside, Mike.
러셀 크로우가 그들을 협박하길 바래야 할거야
You better hope Russell Crowe
is threatening to jump.
좋아, 밑으로 내려가서
부통령의 모습을 보여줘야 돼
All right, we're gonna have to get
her downstairs for an appearance.
안 그러면, 말도 안 되는 추측들을 할 거야
Otherwise, they're gonna
start speculating.
Uh duh duh.
봤지, 완전히 약에 취했다니까
Look, she is fuckin' high
right now.
그녀가 완전히 맛이 간걸
알아 채지도 못했지?
Yeah, yeah.
You didn't happen to notice that
the veep is tripping balls?
개리가 준 약이 항우울증제랑
부작용을 일으켰어.
Gary gave her something that is
reacting with her antidepressants
그리곤 줄리 앤드류스가 됐네
and turning her
into Julie Andrews.
아냐, 그건 그런 게 아냐
No, that's not doing it.
약에서 깰 때까지 여기 잡아둬야 돼
We just need to keep her
here till this thing passes.
게워내게 하면 어떨까?
What if we pump her stomach?
나도 전에 해봤거든
I've had my stomach
pumped before.
내가 할 수 있을 거야
I think I can figure it out.
- 빌어먹을
- Knock, knock, J Rock o'clock!
- Christ.
누가 룸 서비스 시키셨죠?
Yeah, somebody ordered
boom service?
직무상 백악관 상급자로서
As a senior
White House official,
내가 명령을 내릴 거야 마이크.
I am commandeering
this situation, Mike.
좋아, 지금 상황을 설명해봐
All right, what do
you guys got for me?
좋아, 그녀는 투명한 유리문에 부딪혔어,
Okay, she just walked
through a glass door,
보이지도 않는 대선경쟁까지
아이러니 하지,
which is somewhat ironic building
up to an invisible primary,
그리고 섞어먹은 약들에
취해서 정신이 나갔어.
and she is temporarily insane
on a cocktail of happy pills.
이상이야, 대장
Over to you, Captain.
에이미, 방금 그의 뇌를 파괴했네
You just broke his brain, Amy.
맙소사, 저 벌린 입 좀 봐
Jesus, look at his stupid
gaping mouth.
먼가 집어 넣자
Let's put stuff in it.
좋아, 결정 했어
들어봐
Okay, decision.
Listen up.
부통령은 성명을 발표할거야
The veep will make a statement.
그녀는 카메라 앞에서 이 성명을 발표할거야
She will make
this statement on camera
그녀는 할 수 있는 한 빨리
and she will make
this statement
이 성명을 발표할거야
as soon as humanly
fucking possible.
알아 들었어?
Ca-fuckin'-piche?
앤드류, 머가 문제야?
What in the hell
is your problem, Andrew?
왜?
What?
왜 그렇게 쳐다 보는데?
What are you looking
at me like that for?
Your...
- Huh?
- You called me Andrew.
- 저를 앤드류라 불렀어요
아니, 안 그랬거든
No, I did not.
네가 누군지 알아
I know who you are.
네 이름 거꾸로 말 할 수도 있어
I can even say your name
the other way...
나조(Hanoj)
Hanoj.
좋아, 에이미, 이론적으로
네가 처음 처리 해야 할 일이 머야?
All right, academically, Amy,
what's your first move here?
- 마이크, 언론이랑 만나
- 그래, 마이크, 언론이랑 만나
- Mike, go talk to the press.
- Yeah, Mike, go talk to the press.
- 내가 도와 줄게
- 개리 가서 그녀 옷 좀 구해와
- I'll tag team with you.
- Gary, go get her some clothes.
그래, 개리, 가서 부통령 옷 좀 구해와
Yeah, Gary, go get her
some fucking clothes, huh?
어서, 옷 입고 고백할 시간이야
Come on, it's time
to dress up and fess up.
Go, go, go.
내가 잘 처리한 거 같은데
Gotta say, I think
I handled that pretty well.
한낮에 호텔이라니
야릇한 거 같은데
There's something so sexy
about being in a hotel
그렇지 않아?
in the middle
of the day, right?
그래, 4명이 한 화장실을 쓰지.
Yep, four people to one toilet.
오줌 물 튀는 소리도 잘 들리고
You can hear everything
that hits the water.
어디 있는 거야?
옷감 짜고 있냐?
Where the fuck are you?
Picking cotton to weave?
에이미, 그녀를 가릴 만한 게 안보여
Amy, I can't find anything
to cover her up.
터틀넥 옷은 하나도 없네
She doesn't have
any turtlenecks.
4벌 정도로 추렸는데
I've narrowed it down
to four looks.
빨리 와.
Just get back here.
1에서 4까지 숫자 하나 줘봐.
Give me a number between
one and four, please.
- 4
- 나는 3이 더 좋은데
- Four.
- I think I prefer three.
- 그럼 망할 3으로 해
- 4도 괜찮네
- Fucking three, then.
- Actually, four's good.
그럼, 누가 대통령에게 도전할까요?
So, who could
challenge this president?
현재까지, 저희들이 듣기로 후보들은...
At the moment, the names
we're hearing...
세시간이 지났어.
Okay, it has been three hours.
이제 TV 에 나가서 얘기해야 되.
I need her on television now.
그래프라도 그려 줄까, 조나?
Do I need to draw you
a line graph, Jonah?
시간이 흐를수록 약에서 깰 거야
More time equals less cuckoo.
엄한 추측들에 냉정한 진실을 알려야 돼.
We need to take a cold dump
on the speculation.
2년 내에 대통령에게 도전할
Is she the mystery challenger
who's going to throw her hat
신비한 도전자가 부통령인가?
into the ring to challenge
POTUS in two years?
아무도 모자를 던져 도전하지 않을 거 란걸
알려야 한다고.
We need to send the message that
the ring is a hat-free zone.
베레모, 카우보이모자, 비니...
No berets, no Stetsons,
no beanies...
모자 이름은 왜 읊는데?
Why are you just listing hats?
조나 말이 맞아.
Jonah's right.
Ahem.
나가서 엉망인 얼굴을 보여 줘야겠어.
I've gotta put my face
out there, my fucked-up face.
기분 괜찮네.
정말 잘 잤어
I feel so good.
I had such a deep sleep.
보아하니 내가 여기 있어서 다행이네.
Looks like I'll just be sitting
over here being right.
그래, 700일간 함께 일했는데,
딱 한번 쓸모 있군.
Yeah, in 700 days of working
with us, you've been right once.
- 점잖게 앉지 좀, 제발?
- Sit like a gentleman, please?
- Oh, my God.
경치 좋았어요, 마이크?
You like the view, Mike?
여러분 부통령께서 나오십니다.
Okay, everyone.
The vice president.
부통령님
Madam Vice President.
- 자리 좀 만들어 줄래요
- Please, give her some space.
- Hi. Hi, guys.
기다리게 해서 미안하고요,
저는 괜찮습니다.
I'm sorry for keeping you waiting.
I'm fine.
숨기는 건 아무것도 없어요.
I didn't want you to think
I'm hiding anything.
그건 제 스타일이 아니거든요
'Cause that's not my style.
저 에게 일어 난 일은...
What happened is that I, um...
걷다가 유리문에 부딪혔어요
I walked through a glass door.
자존심만 좀 다쳤을 뿐이에요
And the only thing that's
really hurt is my pride.
그때 주변 환경이 어땠나요?
Were there any mitigating
circumstances?
카페트가 깔려 있었나요, 아니면...?
Was there carpeting or...?
- 카페트가 있었던 가, 마이크?
- 네
- Was there carpeting there, Mike?
- Yes.
네, 확인 해 주네요
There was.
Yes, it has been confirmed
카페트가 있었다는 군요
that there was carpeting there.
내일, 달리기를 할거라는데, 맞습니까?
You will be doing the Get
Moving Run tomorrow, correct?
내 최선을 다해 달리려고 합니다.
I fully intend to run.
안돼.
Oh, no,
치질을 철솔로 문지르는 기분이네
that's a fucking
wire brush to my hemorrhoids.
Thank you, ma'am.
그럼, 그녀가 미쳤거나
So she's either crazy
대통령 선거 운동을 시작한 거군
or she's starting
a presidential campaign.
그래, 둘 다 같은 의미야
Yeah, I'd say the two
are synonymous.
‘최선을 다해 달리겠다’?
- - "I intend to run"?
No, no, no.
부통령은 10km 건강 달리기 얘기 한 거에요
She was talking about running
the race, sir, the 10K.
바로잡아, 안 그러면
네 불알을 떼다가 책상 위에 장식해 주지
Fix it or I'll liaise
your balls to your desk.
알겠습니다.
그리고, 감사합니다...
Yes, sir.
And thank you for your continued...
끊었네
he's gone.
Amy, Amy, Amy.
Okay, Amy.
대통령 선거 출마에 대한 억측을 잠재우려면
She needs to run tomorrow
부통령은 내일 건강 달리기에 나가야 돼, 알았지?
to magic away any presidential
speculation, okay?
안돼.
She can't do the Fun Run.
지금도 간신히 서 있는 정도라고.
She can barely do a convincing
walk at the moment.
- 아냐, 할 수 있고 해야 돼.
- 할 수 없고 안 할거 야.
- Okay, can and will.
- Can't and won't.
올라 가서 배게나 채워
Now go up and screw a pillow.
- 방세 지불 했으니
- The room's paid for.
- Oh.
이건 대만에서 온 건데요
And this just in
from Taiwan.
- 무척 재미있어요.
- 먼데?
- So good.
- What?
- 보세요
- Come here.
- What?
-이게 머야?
- Oh.
- What the fuck?
왜 웃는데?
Why are you laughing?
재미있잖아요
I love cartoons.
Jesus.
- That's you, Gary.
- Shut up.
- 이건 너야, 개리
- 닥쳐
전혀 안 닮았어
That doesn't even look
like the Leviathan.
또 머가 있지
다른 문제가 있나?
What else you got?
Is there anything else out there?
언론에 늦게 나타난 걸 두고 말들이 있습니다.
Your delay in facing the press
건강에 문제가 있는 게 아닌가 하는
has raised speculation
on your long-term health.
뭐?
What?
부통령직을 계속 할 수 있는지 묻고 있습니다.
They're asking if you're up
to the job, ma'am.
부통령직을 계속 할 수 있냐고?
Am I up to the job?
Ooh, jeez.
- Ooh.
- The leg thing?
- 다리가 저린가요?
- Yeah.
Seriously, I am totally
overqualified for this job.
진지하게, 나 완전히 준비 되 있어.
- 그만둬!
- Stop it!
- You know...
- 멀 그만둬?
- 아무것도 아니에요
- Stop what?
- Nothing.
국방장관이 보내온 꽃이에요
These flowers came for you
from the Secretary
of Defense Maddox.
오, 한번 보자.
Oh, let's see.
‘건강 달리기 잘 하시고
"Good luck with your Fun Run.
출발 신호 때 놀라서 욕 하지 마시길’
Try not to swear when the
starter pistol goes off."
- 불어 터진 좆 같은 넘이야
- Come on.
- He's just a varicose dick vein.
이 넘은 참을 수가 없어.
좋아, 제군들, 가지
I can't stand that guy.
All right, let's go, guys.
멕시칸 카라오케 식당에 갔었는데
I went to a Mexican
karaoke restaurant
레너드 코헨의 ‘할렐루야’를 불렀거든
and I did "Hallelujah"
by Leonard Cohen.
설마요.
Oh, no, you didn't.
불렀다니까, 그리곤
‘할렐루야’를 ‘할라페뇨’로 바꿨지
I did, and I changed
the "hallelujah"
to "jalape?."
정말 재미있네요.
Oh ho ho! I can imagine
that was very funny, sir.
맙소사, 위원회가 열렸군
Oh, Christ.
It's the Committee.
대통령 조사에 투표할거야
They're gonna vote
on the POTUS investigation.
괜찮을 거에요
Yeah, I think
that's gonna be fine, sir.
물론 그렇겠지, 조나.
Yeah, of course you do, Jonah.
너는 복잡한 건 모르잖아
You don't get the complexity.
너는 세상에 가장 큰 단세포 생물이니까.
You're the world's biggest
single-cell organism.
헤이, 에이미, 국무부에 슈미트 알지?
Hey, Amy, you know Schmidt
at the State Department?
그가 내부 고발자야.
He's the whistleblower.
Yeah.
대통령은 궁지에 몰릴 텐데
POTUS is gonna be up Shit Creek
주변에서 서성이다 이용당하진 않을 거야
and I am not hanging around
to be his fucking paddle.
- 안 그럴 거라고
- 그렇게 되진 않을 거에요, 부통령님
- I'm not.
- It's not coming to that, ma'am.
알 수 없잖아.
내 말은
We don't know.
All I'm saying is that
there are going to be difficult
choices to make, you know?
‘소피의 선택’에서 선택처럼,
어려운 선택이 될 거라는 거지, 알겠어?
Like "Sophie's Choice" choices,
중요한 건 결국 내가 선택하게 될 거란 거야
except more important because
it's gonna be about me.
모두 안녕하세요!
Well, hey there!
좋아요
훌륭해요!
All right.
Great!
- 준비 됐어요, 부통령님
- All right, ma'am.
- Okay.
화장을 너무 많이 했는데
She is definitely wearing
too much makeup.
판토마임 배우처럼 보이네
She looks like Marcel Marceau.
맞아. 유리가 있는 거처럼 연기 할 수도 있겠어
Yeah. He couldn't tell the difference
between real glass and air either.
재미 있잖아
Come on, that's fuckin' funny.
- 자리에 준비
- On your marks...
- Wait.
- 저 좀 무섭네요
- Yeah.
- I'm scared.
출발~!
- ...get set, go!
- Yeah. Okay.
해 보자!
- Oh, shit.
- Let's do it!
Yeah, I see you!
I see you.
계속 달려요!
Let's get moving!
맙소사.
같이 달리는 대사 중 한 명이
Oh, Christ.
Did we warn her
한쪽 다리 잃은 퇴역군인 이란 걸
one of the Get Moving
ambassadors
알려줘야 되지 않을까?
was a one-legged veteran?
그는 그녀 뒤에 있어.
절대 못 알아 챌걸
He's behind her.
She's never gonna see him.
잠깐만, 한 다리 장애인을 이기는 게
But wait, does it look good...
좋아 보일까?
her beating a one-legged
guy like that?
아니, 절대로 안 좋아 보여
No, it doesn't look good.
다른 방안에 대해 생각해 둔거 있어?
The alternative is a little
worse, don't you think?
요점은 그녀가 저 남자를 이길 수 있지만
The key is we make it look
like she could beat the guy,
그가 이기도록 양보하는 그림을 만드는 거지
but then she lets him win.
그래, 양보 함으로서 이긴다
그거 좋네
Yeah, a win-win by losing.
That's good.
왜?
Yeah?
Hello?
개리, 그녀가 천천히 달리게 해
Gary, you need to get her
to slow down.
맙소사, 고마워
Oh, thank God.
그녀가 장애인을 이기면 그림이 안 좋아
It looks bad if she's beating
the disabled guy.
알았어
Okay.
부통령님
Hey, ma'am, ma'am.
- 좀 천천히 달리세요
- 왜?
- You gotta slow down.
- Why?
안 좋아 보여요
It looks bad.
머가, 내 얼굴이?
Oh, God, what?
My face.
아뇨, 얼굴은 괜찮아요.
No, your face looks fine.
장애인을 이기려고 하고 있잖아요.
You're beating a disabled guy.
제발. 개리
엄살 부리지마
Oh, come on.
Don't be so hard on yourself, Gary.
맙소사, 그녀를 멈출 수가 없어
Oh, God. I can't stop her.
She's unstoppable.
-국무부 슈미트가 증언하고 있어.
- -
- Dep Sec Schmidt is testifying.
House Judiciary Committee
사법위원회가
탄핵 투표에 대해 논의하고 있어
is discussing
an impeachment vote.
연관된 모든걸 태워버려
이 빌딩도 함께
Burn everything incriminating,
including this building.
백악관 애완동물도 전부 태워 버리고
너희들도 태워버려.
Burn all the White House pets
and then yourselves.
너희들 먼저 태워버려
Burn yourselves first.
조나, 달리기 하는 곳으로 가서
Jonah, you go down
to the race site,
부통령은 대통령 곁을
지킬 거라고 말하게 해
make sure the vice president
says she stands by POTUS.
미스터 라이언,
부통령은 탄핵 투표에 관한 질문에
Mr. Ryan, ensure
that the vice president
어떤 반응도 보이지 말라고 전해
does not respond to any questions
about the impeachment vote.
그건 서로 상반된 주문 인데요
Those are contradictory orders.
지지를 표명하고 뒤로 빠져있게 해
You make sure that she stands
up and she shits back.
- 관련된 모든걸 부인하라고 해
- 알았어요, 그러면 제가 할 일은...
- Refuses to engage at all.
- Okay, so I should...
- 하나를 선택해
- 네가 알아서 해
- Pick a fucking side.
- Use your judgment.
제 전문 분야가 아닌데.
Sir, that's not
my strongest suit.
Aw, Christ.
국무부 슈미트가 방금 발사 버튼을 눌렀어
Schmidt at the State Department
just pushed the button.
슈미트가 증언하는데 동의 했다고
사법위원회가 발표했어
The Judiciary Committee
says he's agreed to testify.
개리한테 다시 연락해
Okay,
give me Gary again.
- 어서, 개리한테 다시 연락해
- 여기 내려줘요
- Please, get me Gary again.
- You know what? Pull over here.
이 사태가 탄핵투표로 이어 질까?
Could this go to
an impeachment vote?
All right, look, you guys go ahead.
좋아, 너희들은 계속 가
개리가 그녀와 연락하는 지 확인 해야 되
We're gonna make sure Gary
keeps up with her. Okay, okay.
- Gary! Gary, come here!
- Gary! Gary!
그녀가 결승선을 통과하자 마자
As soon as she
crosses the finish line,
언론들이 둘러쌀 거야
the press is gonna be
all over her.
- 좋아, 그럼 머라고 해야지?
- 어디 보자
- All right, so what do we say?
- Hang on, hang on.
- 집어 치우고. 가자
- No, no, fuck it. We gotta go.
- No, come on, man.
- Come on!
- Fuck!
Gary!
Gary.
What? What?
사법 위원회가 탄핵투표에 대해 논의 하고 있어
The Judiciary Committee
is talking impeachment vote.
부통령에게 대응책을 얘기해줘야 되
We need to give her a response.
나는 뒤쳐져 있어
계속 얘기했다간, 토할 거 같아
I'm way behind.
If I keep talking,
I'm gonna vomit.
잘 지냈냐
멍청이 로렉스
Jonah?
Yeah. What's up,
you fuckin' Lorax?
헤이, 댄, 부통령에게 다음과 같이
성명을 발표하게 해,
Hey, Dan, if you're trying to
get a statement to the veep,
대통령에게 약속한 책무를 다할 것이며
충분히 지원할 것이다.
it's this... full commitment to
the president, total backing.
안돼,안돼,안돼. 부통령은 그를 지지 할거야
하지만, 지원하진 않을 거야.
No, no, no, no. She will support
him, but she will not back him.
- 그는 독이 든 사과야.
- 안돼, 완전히 지원하고, 완전히 지지해야 되
- He's too toxic.
- No, full backing, full support.
아우, 바지 지퍼가 내 좆을 치즈처럼 갈아.
Oh, God, this zipper is like
a cheese grater on my dick.
하하! 로랙스
Ha ha! Lorax.
그럼 네가 생각하기에
So which one of us do you think
그 멍청이가 누구 말을 따를 거 같나?
Andre the Giant Jagoff
is gonna obey?
- 조나?
- 그래
- Jonah?
- Yeah.
- 너한테 100 달러 걸지
- 정말이야?
- 100 bucks says you.
- Really?
그 놈은 바보야
차에 치이거나 얼굴에 한방도 맞지 않고
일을 해내면 정말 놀랄 거야
He's an idiot.
I'm surprised he gets to work without being
hit by a car or punched in the mouth.
- Hi!
- Excuse me.
Ma'am, Amy says,
"I give my support
부통령님 에이미가 말하길,
‘이 어려운 시기에 대통령에게
나의 지지를 보냅니다.’
to the president in this
very challenging time."
청문회를 존중한다고 강조하는 게 중요해요
Emphasize it's important to respect
the process of the hearing.
거기서 나와야 돼요
She needs a get-out.
현장으로 돌아와서 에이미,
방금 바나나가 나를 추월했어.
Cut to the chase, Amy.
I'm being overtaken by a banana.
숨을 못 쉬겠어.
I can't breathe.
Oh, I can't breathe.
부통령님, 더 빨리 달리거나 속도를 줄이세요
Ma'am, I need you to speed up
or slow down.
결승선에서 바나나와 함께 사진을 찍힐 순 없잖아요
We can't have you in a photo
finish with a banana.
- 맞아
- 코스프레 행사처럼 보일 수도 있어요
- Yeah.
- It's a caption contest waiting to happen.
맞아, 바나나한테 질 순 없지
Yeah, I'm not gonna
get beaten by a banana.
부통령님
Madam Vice President!
- 잘하셨어요
- 고마워요
- Well done.
- Thank you.
- Nice job.
- Not bad, considering, huh?
- Yeah.
운동하니까 기분이 좋네요.
Feels good to get moving, guys.
맙소사, 달리고 나니 피가 잘 도나 보네요
Oh, my God, it gets
the blood pumping.
건강한 삶을 원한다면
You know, the key really,
folks, to a healthy lifestyle
정답은 운동이에요
- is exercising well.
- Hoo!
- 탄핵 소문에 대해 하실 말씀은 없으신 가요?
- Thank you.
- Any comment on the impeachment rumors?
물론, 내가 아는 모든 것들을
밝힐 거에요
I, of course, have given
my full account
of what I knew
그리고 확신하는데
and now I'm sure
대통령도 그럴 거에요
the president will do the same.
끝났습니다, 끝났어요
That's it, that's it.
손을 머리위로 올려봐
Come on, put your hands
above your head.
Put your... get them up.
이봐, 친구. 가지
Come on, buddy. Let's go.
부통령님 잘하셨어요
- Mike, come on.
- Well done, ma'am.
이제 끝났어
I am done.
음흠.
부통령님 모두 끝났어요
Mm-hmm.
Yes, ma'am, you're all done.
내 말은 이제 끝났어
모든 것을 끝내겠다고
I mean I am done.
I am done with all of it.
부통령직...
잊어 버려
The vice presidency...
I mean forget it.
정말로, 에이미
Seriously, Amy.
무슨 일이 생길지 알잖아, 그렇지?
You can see what's
coming, can't you?
대통령은 나를 모든 것에 연루 시킬 거야
He's gonna implicate me
in all of this.
모든 것에
All of it.
그 후엔, 내가 경멸하는 이놈 곁에서
And then it's gonna be
two years of standing
2년을 보내야 한다는 거지
next to this man that I loathe.
혹시 약에 취해서 하시는 얘기인가요?
Is this just
the St. John's Wort talking?
나를 봐.
상처 투성이에
Look at me.
I'm covered in scabs.
몸에선 땀에 절은 냄새가 나
I smell like a hobo's craphole.
잊어버려
Forget it.
2년 동안 그와 함께 하고 싶지 않아
I'm not gonna run
with him in two years.
그 놈 곁에서 부통령직을 맡기 싫어
I'm not gonna be
his vice president.
이제 끝났어
I'm finished.
6년 후에 돌아 올 거야
I'll come back in six years
그리곤, 내가 정당을 수렁에서 구하는 거야
and I'll save the party
from itself.
그런데, 내 달리기 기록은 어떻게 나왔어?
Hey, do you know what my
time was, by the way?
- 어떤 게 좋은데요?
- 8분에 1마일 정도
- Uh, what's good?
- Like an eight-minute mile.
- 그 정도에요
- 그래?
- That.
- Yeah?
좋아, 이제 움직이자
Yeah, let's get moving...
Oh.
Oh, my God.
정말 힘들었어요
That was really rough.
Hey, Mike,
기억이 가물가물 한데 말이지
I have some sort of hazy memory
내가 네 보트를 산다고 약속을...
of me promising to buy your...
your boat.
네, 그러셨어요
잘 기억하시네요
Yeah, you did.
Well remembered.
그런 일은 없을 거야
That's not gonna happen.
그 문제로 나를 괴롭히지 마, 알겠지?
You can't hold me
to that, right?
그럼요, 물론이죠
Yeah, no.
Sure. Of course.
그거 기운 빠지겠네
Man, that is low.
골아 떨어져 버린 사람이랑
섹스 하려는 기분이겠군
That's like trying to have sex
with somebody who's passed out.
Hey, ma'am, ahem...
제 부모님 파티 말인데요
about my parents' party...
머? 네 부모님 돌아가신 걸로 아는데
What? I thought
your parents were dead.
- 아닌데요
-아냐?
- No.
- No?
No. Um...
곧 40번째 결혼 기념일인데
It's their
40th wedding anniversary
부통령님이 오셔서 춤도 추고,
and you wanted to come and
we were gonna go dancing.
큰 파티가 될 거에요
You know, it's gonna be
a big blowout.
근데, 난 미국의 부통령이야
Okay, I'm the Vice President
of the United States.
-맞아요
-너도 알지?
- Yeah.
- You know.
내 직원들의 가족들 잔치에
I can't be running off
to shindigs
참석 할 순 없어
put on by the parents
of people on my staff.
무슨 말인지 알지?
You know what I mean?
That's completely...
- 완전히 터무니 없잖아
- Yeah, sure.
- ...absurd, you know?
이전에 네 부모님에 대해선
한번도 언급한 적 없잖아
I mean, you've never... never even
mentioned your parents before.
그래서 그들이 돌아가셨다고 생각했거든
I've just always assumed
that they were dead.
왜 안 그렇겠어?
I mean, why wouldn't
I make that assumption?
-그렇지?
-맞아요
Why wouldn't you, right?
Yeah, totally. Yeah.
잠시 돌아가서
Let's get back for a second here...
- 네 부모님 살아 계시다고?
- 그래
- Your parents are not dead?
- No.
너희도 그렇게 생각했다니 재미 있네.
It's so funny that you thought
that they were too.
난 네가 입양 된 줄 알았는데
I thought you were adopted.